a break-up comeback scrooge food ran a full no doubt about it
分手卷土重来的杂粮毫无疑问地跑了整整一整天
last month at several requests for a video about break-ups he think we can
上个月，在一些关于分手视频的要求下，他认为我们可以
get a lot of information from philosophy to make n break up a bit more parable so
从哲学中获得大量信息，使n分崩离析，因此
i've decided to make a series about their looking at the fun for life is to
我决定制作一系列有关他们对生活乐趣的看法，
see what wisdom the fierce sacrifice and recourse to getting over a break-up
看看激烈的牺牲和求助于分手的智慧
led store or with stoicism
领导商店或坚忍不拔
[Music]
[音乐]
the concert of love and romance he is change magic centuries and ancient
爱情和浪漫的音乐会，他改变了魔法世纪和古代
greece he did there was a dating coach there similar to the mayhew well
希腊，他确实在那里有一位约会教练，与mayhew很好
nonetheless i think we can bring and giving them to certain unicorn motions
尽管如此，我认为我们可以带给他们一些独角兽的动作
like last driving attachment or other that haven't
例如上次驾驶附件或其他没有的附件
changed and like you mens nature has died all the time in the world anyway
改变了，就像你一样，男人的天性在世界上一直在消亡
civilization mix ran and ran tracks of physiology is a furry dare and t '
文明混血跑来跑去，生理痕迹是毛茸茸的
van word was like one die 500 years ago that's why in ancient philosophy lek
van word就像500年前的一个死者，这就是为什么在古代哲学里
stoicism is silent applicable yes i know much more now about keep it
坚忍是沉默的适用，是的，我现在知道更多关于保持它
brain works what the thousand take away the validity of story quests do
大脑有效地完成了千篇一律的故事任务
now that's it is essential to the contract was exec lee happening where you
现在，这对合同至关重要，执行董事李发生在您所在的地方
break-up and why reviews at the nou fall in love is a very intense
分手以及为什么在nou坠入爱河的评论非常激烈
experience of body spray djoez 'chemicals that make you feel good and that some
身体喷洒德约兹'化学物质的经验，使您感觉良好，并且有些
point the only person who could think about is the one who you're in love with
指出唯一能想到的人就是你所爱的人
so icing this for a great part is a camping was the purpose of bonding
所以在很大程度上结冰是露营
entry production that's why after also honeymoon
入门产品，这就是为什么在度过蜜月之后
face that is intense feelings' starts your one and see some step that all person
充满紧张感的面孔开始你的一看，看到所有人都迈出的一步
floor rose calorie glasses so is the temporary
地板玫瑰卡路里眼镜是暂时的
hi after the high score carsoft a silent deep attachment is this attachment ronin
嗨，在高分的carsoft之后，这个附件ronin是一个无声的深深依恋
itself at some point weekend really help it right it's there is der met can
周末自己在某个时候真的很有帮助，因为碰到了可以
change the way you approach so attachment and the situation in which
改变您的处理方式，依恋和情况
were separated from the personal touch this is where the power of the rational
与个人风格分开，这就是理性的力量
minecon are white storks or master led even though i can just make up a magic
我只不过是个魔术师，我的孔雀是白鹳还是主人带领的
league ow what helps is changing rips and ram believes in order to accept the
联盟所能帮助的是改变裂痕，而拉姆认为为了接受
reality of the break up and find a scent of peace and at a doctor briefly discuss
分手的现实，找到一种和平的气味，并在医生那里简短地讨论
or use of these beliefs and the steam x ca builds him what he does not
或利用这些信念，蒸汽x ca使他建立了他不知道的东西
person to be happy this attachment can manifest it in yourself
使这种依恋感到高兴的人可以在你自己身上体现出来
clinic behavior and the belief that who is not this particular person to be happy
临床行为和相信谁不是这个特定的人会感到幸福
the common answer to this problem is darth plenty of fish in the sea this
这个问题的常见答案是海中有很多鱼
is of course true wimps already and reason why the sensei
当然已经是真正的imp夫了，为什么老师
then frank that sony and person for you knew something
然后坦白说，索尼和你的人知道一些事情
a thousand oil types problem picas no matter if there's one ten
一千种油的问题，不管有十种
war trillion efficiency the us standstill external
战争万亿效率美国停顿外部
so fioretti the quiet postman the weekend at his any of the space
如此安静的邮递员菲奥瑞蒂（Fioretti）周末在任何空间
even if there's plenty of dan is beyond control
即使有很多丹是无法控制的
info software for my break up because i believe that who you are not the other
我的分手信息软件，因为我相信你不是谁
person to be happy who make the mistake of thinking that ar
认为自己犯了错误的快乐的人
happiness deep and sometimes santing external this is war stoicism family disagrees
内心深处的幸福，有时是外在的痛苦，这是战争禁欲主义家庭的不同意
with according to strong philosophy virtue
凭着坚强的哲学美德
the only thing you need to be happy is about living virtuous life
你唯一需要快乐的事情就是过上美德生活
complete lipocontrol romance or relationship
完整的减脂恋爱或恋爱关系
marriage and even heaven family or all all necessary for happiness and there
婚姻，甚至是天堂般的家庭，或所有幸福和一切必要的一切
also and relive of factors the stoic school that spray kind of indifference
也和重温因素喷洒了那种冷漠的坚忍派
preferred en differnz to seamstress half but not mandatory for
相对于裁缝，首选en区别，但不是强制性的
live happy life to time and title to that
依时过上幸福的生活，并以此为标题
person nou this she stayed for the idea that i focus on line of fire and people it
Nou这个人，她留下来的想法是，我专注于火线和人们
could be that will begin to see the other person essay processes of at least
可能会开始至少看到其他人的作文过程
effector a live.ly ar and tidal to this idea if the ghost was their hand
如果鬼是他们的手，效应者将成为一个活泼的人，并潮起潮落。
chelsea hats basically a pair of los in this person die size to break up with
基本上，这个人一双洛斯死的大小与
as you feel around and finger reasons for the break-up is in some way and just in
当您感觉到周围和手指破裂的原因时，某种程度上
case of the force white especialy fell because
的情况下，白色的力量下降尤其是因为
picasso ex-pope broke the promise of stone to gather and tail and offers die
毕加索前任教皇打破了石头聚集和拖尾的承诺，并提出了死刑的要求
already so interrupt on a fox divorce profile offers reason things like monogamy
因此，对狐狸离婚档案的打扰提供了诸如一夫一妻制的理由
and sexual exclusivity haven't already tied the norm that summer concept uplight
和性排他性还没有束缚夏季概念的亮点
a social structures and part of for example
社会结构，例如
religious traditions and because of this concept already a partner for normative
宗教传统，由于这个概念，已经成为规范的合作伙伴
framework of course this field is sense of in thailand and fair of love and to
当然，该领域的框架在泰国具有一定的意义，并且充满爱意和
this day and age with before and creasing sexual freedom worldwide
当今时代，世界范围内的性自由日趋减少
dating apps the decline of sacred dance and regards to
约会应用神圣舞蹈的衰落和问候
manage chances of ipad relationships fully
全面管理ipad关系的机会
gate so buy break-ups or more and more and so on
门，所以买分手或更多，依此类推
is infidelity fuel oil for everyone's effect
是不忠的燃油，每个人的影响
wise words to say about how we should possess can cells to losing the fifth
明智的话说我们应该如何拥有可以失去第五个细胞
wheel of die quote never say of any thing i've
车轮报价永远不要说我有什么
solve what or return it is your child at this
解决这个问题或返回的是您的孩子
return is your wife third she is return is your stay to sign
回报是你的妻子，她是她的第三次回报。
we do and is not the likewise return what he you
我们做到了，而不是同样地回报他你
to do elizabeth my of difference if you could i give rise
如果可以的话，去做我与众不同的伊丽莎白
to take it back wali get it to you to possess take care
把它拿回去wali得到它，拥有照顾
or ate with don duty jerome just as travelers
或像旅行者一样与唐·杰罗姆一起吃饭
view hotel and quote 3 already never get over that person die
查看酒店并报价3已经永远不会克服那个人死
excuse ring pain to the break up brinks mix team almost impossible to
借口让戒指痛到分手的边缘混合团队几乎不可能
get over it what the clichés juror real-time niels
克服陈词滥调的实时尼尔斯
the wind and stoke philosopher and tension roman emperor marcus garvey spits at
风和斯托克哲学家和紧张罗马皇帝马库斯·加维吐口水
something for russian enthusiastic and otherwise old fat together for the narcissist
对于俄罗斯狂热者和自恋者来说是另外一些老胖子的东西
is already gone change and phlox chancellor remake the world just as the
变革已经不复存在，福禄克总理重塑了世界，就像
incessant progression of time remix author natty and quote
时间不断的发展，混音作者natty和quote
well the penis santing who can wordpress finding it won't help in cities
好吧，阴茎阴茎谁可以通过WordPress发现它在城市中无济于事
better to acknowledge that there some people on lyra libed buy mechanisms
最好承认，有些人在天琴座上拥有自由购买机制
and you study that you espèce dragonfly lots of alcohol and other
然后研究发现您会躲藏大量的酒精和其他蜻蜓
mind trick substances that so just quick fixes led lives help a longer
可以快速解决问题的技巧，可以帮助延长寿命
waste so isolated myself or the after break-up which is only good at it
浪费如此孤立的自己或分手后的分手，这只是擅长的
moderation for my experience ai you share
适度分享我的经验
how the growth fishing combination or active engagement with the world and the
成长性捕鱼的组合或如何与世界和
moment in solitude to really set wit the letter is important
独处的那一刻真的很机智，这封信很重要
is the a brace of vs and to simply and expensive detachment face you need them
是vs的支撑物，要简单而昂贵的分遣队，您需要他们
Process closed the license plate month or evil yours
流程关闭了一个月的车牌或邪恶的你
in order to learn more about how the story's looked at the media group
以了解有关该故事如何看待媒体集团的更多信息
catherine and 14 the event white de churn te celica celica was not just a
凯瑟琳（Catherine）和14岁的白德·塞恩·塞利卡（celica）不仅发生在
story philosopher jos as we kept getting my although who ran
故事哲学家乔斯，因为我们一直在追寻我，尽管谁跑了
our position in the roman empire the whole was charged with a dead tree
我们在罗马帝国的地位整个被控死树
with the emperor's sister like excel chair corsica your
和皇帝的姐姐一样，像excel chair可西嘉岛你
eyes to his mother to console her because she mond is absence
目光投向他的母亲安慰她，因为她蒙德不在了
agreed and now the die must not a while letter
同意了，现在死了一定不要写信
jaron its first prize birds last from variants
贾伦（Jaron）的第一羽冠军鸽来自变种
from console asian my theory t bed and f you to it
从控制台亚洲我的理论床和你到它
for in the seasons also there is nothing more oord full of madison
因为在各个季节中，也没有什么比麦迪逊更重要了
applied to shoot he knows it before a teletext
申请拍摄他在电视文字广播之前就知道了
itself myzone silent and be weekend by time
myzone本身保持沉默，并会在每个周末
so it was able to bear emily's how the lion itself handled and touched
所以它能够承受艾米莉的狮子自身的处理和触动方式
en squad simply put led de tears flow be you and first and one i in michel
他们只是简单地把泪水流向了你，第一个和一个我在米歇尔
jaques whose let see or bump philosophy can be
那些让我们见识或颠覆哲学的杰克
applied as a badge to the thank you for watching route
用作徽章感谢您的观看路线
[Music] [Applause]
[音乐] [掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]